http://www.gotprint.com/store/privacy.html

We recommend that you use the latest version of a modern web browser to ensure you are able to access all of the features and functionality of our website. Continuing to use your existing browser may not allow you to take advantage of certain features.
Click to download any of the following browsers:
Your shopping cart includes at least one disqualified item that will not be kept and cannot be restored upon your next visit. Are you sure you want to proceed with logging out?
CANCEL
PROCEED
Hello Mobile User=Hello Mobile User!
Use our DESKTOP VERSIONandGET 10% OFFup to $100
Use code: THX10
We are working to accommodate mobile orders very soon!
X
Back
Home
Browse All Products
Business
Cards
Marketing
Materials
0
Group 7Created with Sketch.
One moment while we process this request. Please do not refresh the page or press the back button.
HomeCompanyPrivacy
Privacy Policy
Effective Date: August 3rd, 2020
Printograph, Inc. d/b/a GotPrint ("GotPrint," "we," "our," or "us") provides this Privacy Policy to describe how we collect, use, share, and otherwise process the personal information
of individuals who visit our websites, located at www.gotprint.com, www.printograph.com, and www.interfirm.com, use the Printograph app,
interact with any of our services that link to this Policy, or interact with other websites that link to this Policy (collectively "Services").
What information do we collect?
We collect information that you voluntarily provide to us, including your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, fax number, payment card information, employment information,
and any other information that you choose to provide us.
If you create an account on our Services, we also collect your log-in information, such as your username and password.
We collect this
information when you sign up for our Services, contact us, or interact with us in any other manner.
We collect technical information including, but not limited to, browser type, IP address, pages visited and other activities on the Services, device type, and time and date of visit.
We may use cookies or similar technologies to collect such information for advertising and other purposes.
How do we use your information?
We may use your personal information for various purposes, including the following:
To provide the products or services you request, such as to offer our products to you;
To contact you, including to respond to your inquiries;
For business purposes, such as analytics, research, advertising and marketing, payment processing, and operational purposes;
To maintain, operate, customize, and improve the Services;
To comply with law enforcement and maintain the security of our Services; or
As otherwise disclosed at the time of collection or use.
Do we share your information?
We may share the personal information with third parties, including:
With third-parties that provide services on our behalf;
As part of a sale, merger or acquisition, or other transfer of all or part of our assets including as part of a bankruptcy proceeding;
Pursuant to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process or as otherwise required or requested by law, regulation, or government authority programs, or to protect our rights or the rights or safety of third parties; or
With your consent or as otherwise disclosed at the time of data collection or sharing.
We may share information that has been de-identified or aggregated without restriction.
Analytics
We may work with third parties that collect data about your use of our Sites and other sites or apps over time for non-advertising purposes.
GotPrint uses Google Analytics and other
third-party services to improve the performance of our Sites and for analytics and marketing purposes.
For more information about how Google Analytics collects and uses data when
you use our Site, visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners, and to opt out of Google Analytics, visit tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Third-Party Links and Tools
The Services may provide links to third-party websites or apps, including social media pages.
We do not control the privacy practices of those websites or apps, and they are not
covered by this privacy notice.
You should review the privacy notices of other websites or apps that you use to learn about their data practices.
The Services may also include integrated social media tools or "plug-ins," such as social networking tools offered by third parties.
If you use these tools to share personal information or
you otherwise interact with these features on the websites, those companies may collect information about you and may use and share such information in accordance with your account settings,
including by sharing such information with the general public.
Your interactions with third-party companies and your use of their features are governed by the privacy notices of the companies
that provide those features.
We encourage you to carefully read the privacy notices of any accounts you create and use.
California Privacy Rights
This section contains disclosures required by the required by the California Consumer Privacy Act ("CCPA") and applies only to "personal information"
that is subject to the CCPA ("California Personal Information").
Personal Information We Collect.
In the preceding 12 months, we collected the following categories of personal information about California consumers.
Categories of Personal Information
Disclosed for business purposes to the
following categories of third parties:
Personal and online identifiers (such as first and last name, email address, or unique online identifiers)
All categories listed below.
Categories of information described in Section 1798.80(e) of the California Civil Code (such as physical characteristics or description, insurance policy number, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information)
All categories listed below.
Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law (such as race or gender)
All categories listed below.
Commercial or transactions information (such as records of personal property or products or services purchased, obtained or considered)
All categories listed below.
Internet or other electronic network activity information (such as browsing history, search history, interactions with a website, email, application, or advertisement)
All categories listed below.
Biometric information (such as call recordings)
All categories listed below.
Geolocation information
All categories listed below.
Professional or employment-related information
All categories listed below.
Inferences drawn from the above information about your predicted characteristics and preferences
All categories listed below.
Other information about you that is linked to the personal information above
All categories listed below.
Categories of Sources.
We collect California Personal Information from the following categories of sources:
Consumers;
Data analytics providers;
Service providers; and
Our affiliates.
Why We Collect, Use, and Share California Personal Information.
We use and disclose the personal information we collect for our commercial and business purposes,
as further described in this Privacy Policy.
These commercial and business purposes include, without limitation:
Our commercial purposes, including marketing, advertising, and enabling commercial transactions.
Our business purposes as identified in the CCPA, which include:
Auditing related to our interactions with you; Legal compliance;
Detecting and protecting against security incidents, fraud, and illegal activity;
Debugging;
Performing services (for us or our service provider) such as account servicing, processing orders and payments, and analytics;
Internal research for technological improvement;
Internal operations;
Activities to maintain and improve our services; and
Other one-time uses.
Recipients of California Personal Information.
We disclose the categories of personal information designated above to
the categories of third parties listed below for business purposes:
Service providers; and
Data analytics providers.
Your Rights Regarding Personal Information.
California residents have certain rights with respect to the personal information collected by businesses.
If you are a California resident, you may exercise the following rights regarding your personal information, subject to certain exceptions and limitations:
The right to know the categories and specific pieces of personal information we collect, use, and disclose about you; the categories of sources from which we collected personal information about you; our purposes for collecting personal information about you; the categories of personal information about you that we have disclosed for a business purpose; and the categories of third parties with which we have shared personal information.
The right to request that we delete the personal information we have collected from you; and
The right not to receive discriminatory treatment for the exercise of the privacy rights conferred by the CCPA.
To exercise any of the above rights, please contact us using the following information and submit the required verifying information, as further described below:
By phone at 1(877) 922-7374 or email at Privacy@GotPrint.com.
Verification Process and Required Information.
Note that we may need to request additional information from you to verify your identity or understand the scope of your request,
although you will not be required to create an account with us to submit a request or have it fulfilled.
We will require you to provide, at a minimum identifying information to match the personal
information GotPrint maintains about you.
Authorized Agent.
You may designate an authorized agent to make a CCPA request on your behalf by submitting this [Form] via email at Privacy@GotPrint.com.
Minors’ Right to Opt In.
We do not have actual knowledge that we sell the personal information of minors under 16 years of age.
Nevada Privacy Rights
Under Nevada law, Nevada residents may submit a request directing us to not make certain sales of personal information we maintain about them. Nevada residents may opt out of the sale of certain personal
information which includes personally identifiable information such as first and last name, physical address, email address, telephone number, social security number, an identifier that allows you to
be contacted either physically or online, or other contact information that allows us to identify you personally. We do not currently engage in such sales, but we will keep your request on file if
our practices change in the future.
To exercise this right, please contact us:
By phone at 1(877)922-7374.
By email at
Privacy@GotPrint.com.
Your Choices
To update your contact information or change your communication preferences, including to stop email, telephonic, or mail communications from us, you can update your preferences by accessing
"My Account" under "My Profile" or by contacting us through the methods provided in our Contact Us form.
You may also unsubscribe from our email
communications by using the link provided in the email.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
If our information practices change, we will post these changes on this page.
We encourage you to visit this page periodically to learn of any updates.
Contact Us
If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at Privacy@GotPrint.com.
